♪ I'm going down to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks without temptation ♪
♪ Going down to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting "howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ Headed on up to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park ♪
♪ And meet some friends of mine ♪
-=风软FRM字幕组=-
听译:无伤 校对：无伤 iTunes：Tearemix
双语合成 Lv&daisy
好啦 就是这个地方
All right, let's try over here.
把索子捆在这里 还有那里
Set up traps there and there as well.
上次我见到它的时候 就是在这个地方
Last time I saw him, he ran right through here.
这也太扯了吧 cartman
This is so retarded, Cartman.
你居然把大家都骗得团团转
You've got everyone believing your stupid story.
我才没骗人呢 我说的是真的！
It isn't a story, it's true.
我看见了一个小妖精
I saw a leprechaun.
三天前 就在这个地方 可惜它跑掉了
I've seen him come through here three days in a row, now.
鹰眼 我是龙息
Hawkeyes, this is Dragonwind.
你那准备得如何了？
Do you copy?
我是鹰眼
This is Hawkeyes.
我们现在正在吊网呢
We've set up the net and we're standing by.
继续努力 鹰眼
Copy that, Hawkeyes.
千万不要松懈
Keep surveillance tag alpha-niner.
龙翼完毕
Dragonwind out.
快承认你自己的谎言吧 cartman
Just admit you were lying, Cartman,
这样大家都可以回家了
so that everyone can go home.
噢 才不呢 我们可是有协议的哦 kyle
Oh, no, we have a deal, Kyle.
如果世上真的有小妖精的存在
If I can prove there's a leprechaun,
那你可就要舔我的蛋蛋 别忘了哦
you have to suck my balls, remember?
龙息呼叫小黑黑
Dragonwind to Blackie.
那边情况如何？ 小黑黑
What's your six, Blackie?
我不想被叫做“小黑黑”
I don't want the code name "Blackie."
顺其自然吧 小黑黑
Code names are what they are, Blackie.
仔细观察你的四周
Check your six and alert when in position.
这也他妈太蠢了吧？
This is fucking retarded.
哈哈 紧张了是吧 kyle
Getting nervous, Kyle?
只要小妖精一出现 你就非得舔我的蛋蛋不可
When that leprechaun shows up you must suck my balls.
别忘了我们可是签了合同的哦
Don't forget, I have a signed contract from you.
没错 如果你不能证明
Yeah, and if you couldn't prove
小妖精的存在的话 你就要给我10块钱
there was a leprechaun, you had to give me $10.
快把钱给我吧 不要再装啦
Now just pay up and stop being stupid!
日哦 它怎么还不出现呀
Goddamn it, why hasn't it shown up yet?
龙息呼叫娘娘腔
Dragonwind to Faggot, come in, Faggot.
这是娘娘腔
This is Faggot.
请讲
Go ahead.
娘娘腔 我需要你多注意东北方
Faggot, I need you to keep surveillance north, northeast.
有情况就及时汇报！
Check back in five.
好的 没问题
Okay, will do.
娘娘腔完毕
Faggot out... Ugh.
好啦 我受够了
Okay, that's enough.
各位 cartman不过是在
Everybody... Cartman is just pulling one of his
欺骗大家的感情罢了
stupid tricks on everyone
因为他想混过他的合同!
because he's trying to get out of a deal he made.
它就在这的 我发誓！
It was here, I swear it!
我只是不知道它今天怎么还没出现
I don't know why it's not showing up this time!
你才没见过小妖精呢 死胖子
You didn't see a leprechaun, fat ass!
如果你能证明它的存在的话 我就舔你的蛋蛋
If you could prove it, I had to suck your balls,
可如果你不能 你就得给我十块钱！
and if you couldn't, you had to pay me $10.
给钱
Pay up!
噢 我看见什么啦
I got something!
我看见啦！
I got it!
它看起来好象..我想它应该是个小妖精
It's a-- whoa, jeez, I think it's a leprechaun!
小黑黑 快放陷阱！
Set off diversion trap "c"!
天哪
Dude!
我..我..日.. 真的是小妖精
F- fuck me, it's a leprechaun.
抓住它！
Get it!
抓住这该死的小妖精！
Get that fucking leprechaun!
要活的
I want it alive!
- 酷 - 不可能吧
Wow! - Cool! - No way! - Whoa!
让开 让开！
Move aside, move aside!
好啦 小屁眼 黄金在哪儿？
All right, butthole, where's the gold?
我不知道你们在说虾米啊
You lads don't know what you're doing!
我有份急件要送
I need to deliver an important message!
有一场入侵即将发生！
There's going to be an attack!
快说黄金在哪儿！ 不然你就得死！
Tell me where the gold is or you die...
凌迟！
Slow.
它去哪了？
Where'd he go?!
我本来是要送一份紧急的军机情报的
I was sent to warn of a terrorist attack,
可你们这些臭小子害我把时间给耽误了
but you boys have made me late!
现在恐怖分子就要来啦
Now the terrorists will prevail!
我们要完蛋了
The end is near!
Dude.
Kyle...
舔..我..的..蛋..蛋
Suck my balls.
(南方公园)
(犹太人勇斗肥仔睾丸)
(三部曲)
老爸 小妖精是从哪来的呀?
Dad, where do leprechauns come from?
爱尔兰呀
From Ireland.
那么 他们怎么会跑到美国
So why would one come to America
来报告恐怖分子入侵呢?
to warn us about a terrorist attack?
kyle 小妖精不是真实存在着的
Kyle, leprechauns aren't real.
你都差不多九岁了
You're almost nine now.
该明白真实和幻想
You need to understand the difference
之间的区别了呀
between real and imaginary.
我原来是明白的..
I thought I did.
哈罗 Broflovski太太
Ah, Mrs. Broflovski,
见到您真高兴!
how are you this fine evening?
噢 哈罗 eric
Oh, hello, Eric.
kyle 你的小朋友来啦
Kyle, your friend is here.
哈罗 Broflovski先生 ike
Hello, Mr. Broflovski, Ike.
今晚天气真好呀 不是吗?
Nice evening, isn't it?
恩 kyle 我们可以去你的房间
Well, Kyle, shall we go up to your room
单独聊几分钟吗?
for a few minutes?
滚出去 cartman 我们在吃晚饭呢
Get out of here, Cartman, we're eating dinner.
恩 kyle 我想似乎有些人有义务
Uh, Kyle, I believe a certain someone is supposed to
把某些球状物体放入自己的嘴巴哦
put a certain set of balls in their mouth.
我才不干呢 死胖子
I'm not doing it, fat ass!
干什么?
Doing what?
我们有协议的 kyle
We had a deal, Kyle!
快给我滚出去!
Just get out of here!
你可是签了合同的! kyle
You signed an agreement, Kyle!
我才不理什么鸟合同呢!
I don't care if I signed an agreement!
这样不对哦 kyle 如果你和他人签了合同的话
Hey now, Kyle, if you made a deal with somebody,
就要遵守上面的条款
you have to stick by it.
多谢啦 Broflovski先生
Thank you, Mr. Broflovski.
你们签的合同是什么?
What was the agreement?
如果他能证明小妖精的存在
That if he could prove leprechauns exist
我就添他的蛋蛋
I would suck his balls.
虾...米...!!!
What-what-what?!
而的确小妖精!
And there was a leprechaun!
你看见了 kyle
You saw it, Kyle!
嗨 伙计们
Hey, dudes.
嗨 kyle
Hey, Kyle.
怎样 感觉如何?
So... How was it?
什么感觉如何?
How was what?
舔cartman的蛋..蛋啊?
Sucking Cartman's ba-balls.
我没舔他的蛋蛋!
I didn't suck his balls, all right!
而且我也不准备舔!
And I'm not going to!
那你一开始的时候为什么
Dude, why did you ever agree
要签那种协议呢?
to suck his balls in the first place?
我那时根本不相信有小妖精的存在
I didn't think there would actually be a leprechaun!
而且我现在也不相信!
And I still don't!
小妖精怎么会告诉我们关于
Why would a leprechaun be warning us
恐怖分子入侵的事呢?
of a terrorist attack?
这一切也太无厘头了
There's another explanation for all this.
不好意思哦
Excuse me,
孩子们 你们最近有没见过一只小妖精?
have you boys seen a leprechaun anywhere lately?
你知道什么关于小妖精的事吗?
What do you know about the leprechaun?
噢 那么说你们见过它咯?
Oh, then you did see him!
这实在太赞啦
That's wondiferous!
我希望你们把它说的话都告诉我
I want you to tell me everything he said!
你们在哪见到它的 它那时在干什么?
Where was he? What was he doing?
好啦 我受够啦
All right, I've had enough!
小妖精不过是幻想出来的事物罢了
Leprechauns are imaginary!
没错 它们当然是幻想出来的
Well, of course, they are.
可它们是幻想出来的
But just because they're imaginary,
并不表示它们不是真实的存在
doesn't mean they aren't real!
孩子们 你们有没有开动过自己的想象力?
Haven't you boys ever used your imagination?
你 孩子 难道不想当个牛仔
You, young man, how would you like to be a cowboy
或者是太空舰船长什么的?
or a swashbuckling pirate?
而你
And you!
难道不想当个宇航员
How would you like to be an astronaut
去探索未知的外太空?
far out in space?
这一切 都只需要一点点想象力而已
All it takes is a little imagination.
你到底是谁啊?
Who the hell are you?
还没被我说服吗?
Still not convinced, eh?
我告诉你们哦 孩子们
I tell you what, boys,
不如我们一起去我的
what say we all take a ride on my
幻想飞行器上兜兜风吧
Imagination Flying Machine?
天哪
Dude.
快上来吧 孩子们
Hop aboard, kids!
我可有好东西要给你们看哦
I have something to show you!
厄 你会不会猥亵我们?
Ah, are you gonna rape us?
厄..不会啊..
Ubla... Uh... No.
恩 那就好
Oh, all right then.
快来吧 伙计们
Come on, guys.
小心哦 伙计们
Watch it, fellas.
我很肯定这人想要猥亵我们
I'm pretty sure this guy wants to rape us.
全部上船啦 幻想气球启动!
All aboard the Imagination Balloon!
有些人觉得幻想是不切实际的东西
Some people feel imagination isn't real.
可我要说他们全部都错了
But I tell them that they're wrong!
以为每当我想要开动想象力的时候
'Cause whenever I want to play and pretend,
我都会唱这首
I just sing the
"幻想之歌"
♪ Imagination song ♪
♪ Imagi-na-tion ♪
♪ Imagina-tion ♪
♪ Imagi-nation ♪
♪ Ima-gination ♪
♪ Imagination ♪
♪ Imagina-tion ♪
你到底是要带我们去哪玩 还是怎样?
Are you gonna take us somewhere or not?!
噢..
O-o-oh!
可是 孩子们 我们已经到了呀
But, my boy, we're already here.
!Hoaoa! Whoa!Hoa !Hoaoa! Whoa!Hoa
这是哪呀?
What is this place?
这 就是幻想仙境
This is Imaginationland.
这儿全部都是人类在发展过程中
It's where all the wonderful and goofy things
所想像出来的美好的事物
that humans have made up over the years, live together.
各位幻想仙境的居民们
Citizens of Imaginationland!
我们有幸请到了来自遥远的人间的客人
We have distinguished guests from the world beyond!
你们好
Ooh! - Ahh! - Ooh! - Hello!
欢迎来到幻想仙境
Welcome to Imaginationland.
我是棒棒糖国王
I am the Lollipop King.
很荣幸能见到我们国度的创造者们
We are honored to have creators in our kingdom.
还有好消息哦 各位
Now, good news, everyone.
这些孩子们说他们看到小妖精了!
These boys did see the leprechaun!
Yeah! Woo-hoo ! Woo! Yeah!
小妖精和你们说什么了?
What did the leprechaun tell you?
它有什么情报吗?
Did he have any news?
它说 即将会有..
Well, he said there was gonna be a...
即将会有..
That there was gonna be a--
阿拉!
Allah!
日 不要呀!
Oh, fuck, no!
Augh!
stan 我们得离开这儿!
Stan, we have to get out of here!
快 孩子们 快到我背上来
Quickly, boys, get on my back!
伙计们..
Fellas!
伙计们..等等呀!
Fellas, wait!
别丢下我呀 伙计们!
Hold on, fellas!
Butters!
别抛弃我 伙计们
Don't leave me, fellas!
回来!
Come back!
Ugh!
天哪!
Dude!
butters!
Agh!
怎么回事 哪儿啊
Aghgh! What, where?
噢..天哪
Oh, oh, dude.
还好 只是一场梦罢了
Oh, it was just a dream.
一场疯狂的梦
It was all just a crazy dream.
Oh, my God.
噢..主啊
哈罗?
Hello.
兄弟 数学作业写完了吗?
Dude, did you finish your math homework?
我昨天晚上的时间似乎迷失了
I kind of lost track of time last night.
没呢 我整晚没休息好
No, no, I hardly got any sleep.
我梦到一个基佬
I had this whole messed-up dream
带我们去了个什么幻想仙境
about some gay mayor guy taking us to Imaginationland
所有幻想出来的事物都在那生活着
where all these imaginary characters lived.
然后他们就被恐怖分子攻击了?
And then it got attacked by terrorists?
没错 你怎么知道的?
Yeah, how'd you know?
伙计 我们做了同一个梦!
Dude, I had the same dream!
我们上了龙背
We jumped on a dragon's back
可是butters落下了
and Butters got left behind!
stan stanley..
你最近有没有见过butters呀?
You haven't seen your little friend Butters, have you?
怎么啦?
Why?
我们亲爱的小buttters昨晚一直没有回家
Our darling Butters never came home last night.
他们说什么?
What did they say?!
我们不敢想象后果
We don't want to jump to conclusions,
但很有可能 butters被某些变态绑架了
but we're worried that maybe somebody kidnapped Butters,
被一遍遍的猥亵
sodomized him over and over again
他的小宝贝也很有可能被切下来喂动物去了
and then fed his genitals to wild animals.
别哭了 亲爱的
There, there, darling.
天哪
Dude.
女士们先生们 我有紧急情报
Ladies and gentlemen, I have dire news.
昨天 准确的说是18小时前
Yesterday, at approximately 1800 hours,
恐怖分子成功的入侵了
terrorists successfully attacked...
我们的想象
Our imagination.
我们的想象?
Our imagination?
他们怎么弄的?
How?
他们对这次攻击
The imaginary attack appears to have been
策划了很久了
in the works for years.
至于他们是如何做到的 根本无法想象
The effects of the attack are so far unimaginable.
我们查到了这份恐怖分子
We've intercepted this videotape
制作的录像带
the terrorists made for broadcast.
幸好它没有被公众们看到
Luckily, we've kept it from being broadcast to the public.
不要啊 它不过是只彩虹熊罢了
No, he's just a Care Bear!
Agh!
噢 主啊
Oh, my God.
在录像带的后半部分 我们还可以看见一名想象中的人质
Later in the video, we can see another imaginary hostage,
在读恐怖分子的宣言
this one reading a forced statement.
赞美唯一真主阿拉
"Praise to the mighty Allah.
它创造了整个世界..
His divine grace and will have brought forth this day."
厄..
Whoa, jeez!
看见了没 现在你们的想象都掌握在我们手中吧
"Uh, now see your safety is at our whim.
这就是你们的代价 美国佬!
"this is the price you pay, America!
你们玷污了真主阿拉
"You have defiled Allah,
而我们现在将要摧毁你们的幻想世界!
"and now we shall turn your imagination against you!
干掉异教徒！
Death to the infidels!"
我现在可以走了没?
Can I go now?
stan kyle 快来救我呀!
Stan, Kyle, could-could ya get me outta here?!
先生们 恐怖分子已经取得了
Gentlemen, the terrorists appear to have
我们的幻想世界的全部控制权
complete control of our imagination.
这一切只是时间问题而已
It's only a matter of time before...
我们的幻想世界即将变得疯狂起来
Our imaginations start running wild.
我认为 民主的名义
I believe a serious blow to democracy
正在遭受玷污
has just been dealt.
一个污点正在诞生之中 我需要公证
A travesty has occurred, and I want justice.
??
kyle Broflovski是在知情并且自愿的情况下
Kyle Broflovski did willingly and knowingly
签署这个合同的
sign a contract
可是知道目前为止 他没有表现出
and yet, as to date, he has made no effort,
哪怕是稍微一点点
nor does he show any intention
想要履行承诺 舔我蛋蛋的意思
of ever sucking my balls.
我已经给了他多次机会来兑现承诺
I have given him ample time to fulfill his obligation
可他却一直拒绝
and he has thus refused.
我带着干巴巴的蛋蛋站在您的面前 法官大人
I stand before you with dry balls, your honor.
我已经尽了最大努力与妥协
I have provided witnesses, collected testimonials,
可我的蛋蛋还是干巴巴的
and still my balls remain dry.
我希望得到属于我的东西
I want what I'm entitled to.
Broflovski先生 你是否有签署用嘴部
Mr. Broflovski, did you agree to orally imbibe
接触cartman先生胯下球状物的协议?
Mr. Cartman's scrotum and testicles?
我..
I...
这个合同上面是你自己签的名字吗?
Is this not your signature on the contract?
Uh...
可是..
Oh, uh, but...
拜托..真的要吗?
Come on, really?
我是说 法庭就不能审理点
I mean, aren't there more important things
更重要的案子吗?
going on right now?
就我所得到的证据来看
From what I have been presented and the evidence put forth,
法庭裁定你别无选择 必须得把catman的先生
the court has no choice but to order you to place
胯下的球状物放入自己的嘴里
Mr. Cartman's pubical sack in your mouth
并且要含着它不少于30秒钟
and draw upon it succulently for no less than 30 seconds.
Yes!
你有24小时的时间去添那两个蛋蛋
You have 24 hours to suck aforementioned balls.
如果你到时仍未履行这个合同
If after that time you've still refused,
法庭将会以诈骗罪逮捕你
the court will be forced to arrest you for contempt.
好啦 下一个案子
Next case.
多谢啦 法官大人
Thank you, Your Honor.
这不是我的胜诉
This isn't a victory for me.
这是整个司法系统的胜诉
This is a victory for the justice system...
还有....我的小蛋蛋
And my balls.
我将要告诉你的事情可是高度机密
What I am about to tell you is highly classified.
两天以前 穆斯林恐怖分子劫持了我们的想象
Two days ago Muslim terrorists hijacked our imagination.
我们不知道他们接下来要做什么
Frankly, we don't know what their next move is
如何阻止他们
or how to stop them.
每当遇到这种情况 政府都会
In times like these, the government often turns to
向好莱坞求助
Hollywood for help.
你们这些电影人总是可以想到我们想不到的点子
You creative filmmakers can think of ideas we just can't.
这正是我们找你来的原因
That's why we've asked you here,
Night Shyamalan先生
Mr. Night Shyamalan.
第六感 灵异村庄
The Sixth Sense, Signs, The Village--
都是非常了不起的电影
all very clever films.
但你现在能运用你那神奇的头脑
But can you use your amazing idea brain now
来帮助我们阻止恐怖分子吗?
to help us stop the terrorists?
如果..
What if...
如果实际上他们不是恐怖分子
What if it turns out they aren't terrorists,
而是来自未来的狼人?
but they're actually werewolves from the future?
不呢 他们真的是恐怖分子
No, no, they're terrorists.
他们是穆斯林
They've been linked to Al Qaeda.
可如果实际上穆斯林
But what if Al Qaeda, it turns out,
是由外星人所控制的恐怖分子?
is the group being terrorized... By aliens?
不呀 这才不是什么点子呢
No, that's not an idea.
这是个"曲折的情节"
That's a twist.
我们要的是点子
We need ideas.
那么 也许我们都只是想象自己
How about we make everyone think that
在被恐怖分子攻击而已
terrorists attacked us...
实际上我们早就都死了
But really we were all already dead?
把他赶出去!
Get him out of here.
bay先生 你能想出什么
Mr. Bay, can you think of any ideas
阻止这些恐怖分子的点子吗?
how to outwit these terrorists?
我想我们可以的
I believe I can.
首先 我们用CG做一栋大楼
We start by making a big c-g building,
再让它坍塌
and then we have a meteor go fweoooshh!
然后就是"咔啦! 咔啦!"
And then it's all like crawwwww!
接着是摩托车..
And motorcycles burst into flame
在直升飞机上从天而降
while they jump over these helicopters, right?
不!
No, no.
我们要的是可以阻止恐怖分子的点子!
We need ideas how to stop the terrorists.
一辆18轮大货车忽然失去控制...
An 18-wheeler spins out of control,
"卟啦!"
and it's all like brashshh
然后满车的钻石就
into this huge tanker full of dynamite!
"呵嚨!"
It's like craw-rawwww-boosh...
这些才不是什么点子
Those aren't ideas.
这些是特效!
Those are special effects.
这两者之间有什么区别吗?
I don't understand the difference.
你当然不知道!
I know you don't.
把他赶出去!
Get him out of here!
因为我们都是mel gibson的超级粉丝哦
And being that we are all big Mel Gibson film fans,
所以我想你可以帮助我们
we thought maybe you could help us.
啊 我的小咪咪好痛啊
Oh, my nipples, they hurt!
我一扭它们 它们就好痛呀
They hurt when I twist them!
恩..
Yes, uh...
我也不大指望你能想出什么
I don't suppose you have any creative ideas
可以解决掉恐怖分子的点子
how to fight these terrorists?
这个如何
How about this--
你们有那柄恐怖分子做的录像带呀 不是吗?
you have that video tape that the terrorists made, right?
当你们仔细检查
Well, maybe if you did a background check
那柄录像带的背景时
on the video tape,
也许你们会发现某些人并不属于那个国度
you might find somebody who doesn't belong,
某些人根本不可能在幻想仙境中出现..
somebody who doesn't fit in Imaginationland.
噢!
Oh!
嘿 这主意可不坏!
Hey... That's not a bad idea.
没错
Yeah.
不管你怎么看mel gibson
Say what you want about Mel Gibson,
但这婊子养的知道如何处理剧本结构!
but the son of a bitch knows story structure.
快去把录像带找来
Get the videotape and do a background check
并且仔细检查里面的每一个人!
on everyone in it.
啊!! 真爽啊!
Oh, yes!
录像带中的所有幻想人物
All the imaginary characters in the tape
都已被确认 长官
were identified, sir.
吸血鬼 灰姑娘 来自闪电猫的snarf
Count Chocula, Cinderella, Snarf from Thundercats.
但..这儿
But here.
没有任何一项美国民间传说
Nothing in American folklore
有涉及这个孩子
or story-telling matched this kid.
他应该..就是个孩子而已
He appears to be just some kid.
(stan kyle 你们快来救我呀!)
Stan, Kyle, could-could ya get me outta here?!
我要求所有资料室
I want digital imaging
全线调查!
and resource magnification done stat.
如果这个孩子不是想象出来的
If that kid isn't imaginary,
那我希望知道他是谁
I want to know who he is,
他从哪来 他的朋友是什么人!
where he's from, and who his friends are!
是的 长官!
Yes, sir.
你..是..谁?
Who are you?
厄..不好意思 恐怖分子先生
Uh, excuse me, Mr. Terrorist, sir?
厄 我实际上不是被想象出来的
Uh, I'm actually not imaginary,
而且我父母会惩罚我 如果我没在..
and, um, my parents are gonna ground me if I don't--
啊..
Ahh!
ok..对8起..对8起..
Okay, sorry, sorry!
那些恐怖分子到底在干什么?
Can you tell what the terrorists are doing?
他们好像要把火箭小子捆起来呀
They're doing something to Rockety Rocket!
啊..放开我..啊..
No, leave me alone!
Ahg!
这一切有什么意义呢
It doesn't make sense.
他们要拿火箭小子干什么?
What do they want with Rockety?
他们这样做只有一个理由..
The only reason they would...
噢..主啊..
Oh, my God.
他们将要摧毁防护栏!
They're gonna blow up the barrier!
防护栏是什么?
What's the barrier?
那堵墙 那堵墙分隔了
The wall, the wall which separates
幻想仙境的
the evil side of Imaginationland
美好部分和邪恶部分
from the good side!
不
No!
你们不能摧毁那堵墙 这太疯狂啦
No, you can't blow up the barrier!
你们发疯了吗
Are you insane?!
我们不能坐视不理啊
We can't let this happen!
不然幻想仙境会灭亡的!
It'll be the end of Imaginationland!
没错
Yeah!
你得阻止他们! 孩子
You have to stop them, kid!
我?
Me?
我能做些什么捏?
What am I supposed to do?
你还不明白吗!
Don't you get it?!
如果恐怖分子把那堵墙撞开
If the terrorists blow that barrier,
人类历史所想像过的所有最邪恶的东西
all the most evil things ever imagined
都将出山
are gonna pour out
把幻想仙境的美好部分摧毁得一干二净!
and take over Imaginationland for good!
你必须得做点什么!
You have to do something!
Wahghgh!
感谢各位的到来
Thanks for coming, everyone.
盛大的仪式即将进行
The big moment is almost here,
只要kyle来到现场
as soon as Kyle arrives.
他是不可能会过来舔你的蛋蛋的 伙计
He's not gonna show up to suck your balls, dude.
他必须来
He has to.
法庭已经警告过他了
He's been ordered by the court.
嘿 他来了哦
Hey, he's here.
噢 让开 让开!
Wha-- move aside, move aside!
伙计 你真的准备要做吗?
Dude, do you really have to do it?
我只是想让这件事早些结束!
Let's just get this over with.
噢 快进来吧 kyle
Yes, come on in, Peasant Kyle,
对我的蛋蛋臣服吧!
and pay homage to the Sultan's balls!
我操!
Goddamn it.
Yes...yes!
这就是他们 长官
That's them, sir.
stan marsh和kyle Broflovski
Stan Marsh and Kyle Broflovski.
你们两个孩子得和我走一趟
You boys need to come with us
以国家安全的名义
on a matter of national security.
你们是谁
Who are you?
没时间啦 你们现在就得跟我们走!
There's no time, you need to come with us right now!
嘿 放开他!
Hey, let go of him!
我们不会伤害你的小朋友的
We aren't going to hurt your little friends.
我们只是像他们询问一些信息而已
We just need information.
不!
No!
不行! 他得先舔我的蛋蛋!
No, he has to suck my balls!
不!
No!
不要啊!
阿拉
Allah! Allah ! Allah!
No, no!
稍等
Hold on!
稍等一下好吗
Hold on a second!
你们得认真想想这个问题
Now... You really should think about this.
我是说 你们觉得劫持我们的想象
I mean, uh, I know you think
会给你们带来什么好处
attacking our imagination will get you somewhere,
可是真的会有什么好处吗?
but will it really?
如果你们撞坏那堵墙的话
If you destroy that wall,
一群人类想象史上最邪恶的东西
all the most evil parts of our imagination
都将出来摧毁这个世界
are gonna break loose.
可这样会使你们这些恐怖分子好受点吗?
But will it really make you terrorists feel better?
也许现在正是我们大家开始友好相处的开端呢
Maybe it's time for us all to just... Get along.
啊啦!
Allah! Allah ! Allah!
耶稣基督啊!不要啊！
Arrg, Jesus Christ, no!
Yay!ay Yay! Yay!ay Yay!
这就是你所谓的"阻止"?
That was your plan to stop them?!
是呀 一篇发自内心深处的演讲
Yeah, a nice little heartfelt speech.
这也他娘的太蠢了吧?
That's fucking stupid!
他们要来了..
They are coming.
还好我给你搭了个便车呢 孩子
Glad I picked you up, kid.
像你这么大的孩子一个人上路 可是很危险的
It's dangerous for someone your age to be hitchhiking.
恩 可是当一个人被背叛过以后
Yeah, well, when a man has been wronged...
他就不会在乎什么危险了
He no longer cares about danger.
你到华盛顿是去看你的家人吗?
You goin' to Washington to visit family?
我有些不得不做的事情要完成
I've got unfinished business.
你花费一生的时间去追寻公正
You go through life being told there's justice.
可你最终会意识到
Then you learn that the only real justice...
只有自己争取到的 才是真正的公正
Is the justice you take.
不要心存侥幸 kyle
Make no mistake, Kyle...
在这一切结束之前
Before this is over,
you will suck my balls.
我一定会把蛋蛋放入你的嘴里!
风软FRM字幕组出品
-==http://www.1000fr.com==-
欢迎加入